<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on deciacco</title>
    <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on deciacco</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://deciacco.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Poll Vote - Object Oriented Programming</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/pollvote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/pollvote/</guid>
      <description>Poll Voter is a &amp;ldquo;Bot&amp;rdquo; that automatically votes for a certain, user specified option on an online poll artificially changing the results.
The original code is below with the refactored version in OOP.
Poll Vote Code #!/usr/bin/env python3 # Load libraries import logging import random import datetime import os import sys import time import json import requests from torpy import TorClient from torpy.http.adapter import TorHttpAdapter from bs4 import BeautifulSoup as BeaSoup # Constants RETRIES = 3 OWNP = os.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comcast Modem Power Level Monitor</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/comcastmodemmonitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/comcastmodemmonitor/</guid>
      <description>Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find scripts to monitor a Comcast modem&amp;rsquo;s power levels to help troubleshoot line problems.
The power of this tool becomes apparent when you use the data gathered to maintain an event journal of everything that happens related to your connection.
For example, for my business, everytime I show packet loss in my firewall I can corelate it to abnormal power levels in the modem. This is critical, not only to know that the problem lies outside of my control, but also to aide the Comcast technitians in fixing the issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private GitHub Repo and Autohokey</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/ahkgithubprivate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/ahkgithubprivate/</guid>
      <description>How to connect to a GitHub Private Repository to download files.
This can be useful if you want to automatically update your application to the latest release.
#SingleInstance, force #NoEnv #Include %A_ScriptDir%\..\json\JSON.ahk ;https://github.com/cocobelgica/AutoHotkey-JSON ;------------------------------------------------------------------ ;GLOBALS global g_url := &amp;#34;https://api.github.com/repos/&amp;lt;username&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;repository&amp;gt;/releases&amp;#34; global g_file := &amp;#34;filename.zip&amp;#34; global g_saveto := A_Desktop . &amp;#34;/&amp;#34; . g_file ; You need to generate this in your github account global g_token := &amp;#34;74jf8gh7ihdg9orlkk948rjfugnry369jgirn857&amp;#34; ; &amp;lt;-- not a real token, demo purposes ;------------------------------------------------------------------ ;MAIN CODE r := false request := comobjcreate(&amp;#34;WinHttp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor Folder Service With PHP (Almost)</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/monitorfolderservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/monitorfolderservice/</guid>
      <description>At the office we use a RICOH Aficio 1045 Copier. One of the features of this copier is that it also doubles as a scanner. To scan a document an employee goes to the copier, puts the copier in scanner mode, selects their mailbox from a list and then scans the document. The scanner then sends the scanned information to the scanner software running on one of our servers where the actual file is created and placed in the user&amp;rsquo;s virtual mailbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Mailer - Php Application for Windows (Almost)</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/phpimagemailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/phpimagemailer/</guid>
      <description>Here is a small utility to more easily email photos with Microsoft Outlook. Basically, it allows you to embed images in the body of the email message so that it is easier for the recipient to view the files.
Download the file using the link below. Once downloaded, install it by double-clicking it. To use the program, simply highlight the photos you wish to send, then right-click one of the highlighted images and select &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;Send-To&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; then &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;Image Mailer for Outlook&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Better &#34;Send to Mail Recipient&#34; With Outlook</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/bettersendto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/bettersendto/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes when sending files through email, you want to be able to simply right-click on the file and select Send to mail recipient form the context menu. If you are an Outlook 2003 or 2007 user, you might have noticed that when you do this, Outlook generates a plain text email with your files attached.
While a plain text email is ok, and probably the way all email should be, most of us have been spoiled with html email that allows fancy formatting and we want to keep this functionality when we right-click to send attachments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Resizer - Php Application for Windows (Almost)</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/phpimageresizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/phpimageresizer/</guid>
      <description>Small utility to quickly and easily resize images. Written in PHP, and while PHP is mostly a &amp;ldquo;Web&amp;rdquo; language, it actually worked out quite nicely.
You simply right-click an image or a folder containing images and select the appropriate command. Currently, the program supports JPEG, GIF, and PNG images.
The original image remains intact as a new, resized version is created.
Installing
You can simply download the installer and run it on your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LblPrint</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/lblprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/lblprint/</guid>
      <description>This is a very simple label printer application.
Here is how it works:
The user enters a search term, then clicks the search button. The program connects to the Sql Server 2000 database, retrieves the data, and populates the data grid. The user then selects the record desired and the label preview is generated.
On every record selection the preview is automatically generated. The user can then select a modifier by clicking on one of the radio buttons to the right of the preview container.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP Ftp Backup Library</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/phpftpbackuptool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/phpftpbackuptool/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE 2019-11-07: This is a tool I used for work many years ago. At the time I was not happy with what was available to do backups for my company. This tool allowed our critical files to be automatically sent off-site on a nightly basis. Things have come a long way since then!You can take a look at the documenation here:
Documentation Link(Use the dropdown in the top, right to switch between the two objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C# .NET 2.0 Web Service - Sync &#43; Async</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/dilbertsycasync/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/dilbertsycasync/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to learn how to use web services in .NET with C#, so I created this tiny program that goes out and gets the &amp;ldquo;Dilbert of the Day&amp;rdquo; comic strip and puts it on your desktop in the form of a jpeg file.
There are two versions to this program. One calls the web service synchronously, while the other calls the web services asynchronously. Synchronous calls are what most programmers would be familiar with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BatchRun</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/batchrun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/batchrun/</guid>
      <description>This application was written to run multiple sql scripts files against an MS Sql Server database. I wrote it to learn more about .NET C# 2 Windows application development.
It is pretty much a work in progress, but it&amp;rsquo;s at a usable point.
Repository</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP, OpenSSL and ftp_ssl_connect() on Win32</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/phpopenssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/phpopenssl/</guid>
      <description>For quite some time I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to compile PHP for the sole purpose of using the http://us.php.net/ftp_ssl_connect function.
According to the PHP manual:
When I first saw this I was disappointed. I thought I would never be able to compile PHP myself. It just felt like a daunting task to get my system configured correctly.
&amp;hellip;Well, it&amp;rsquo;s not perfect, but I have been able to get it to work, and I&amp;rsquo;ve even been able to patch up the PHP code itself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UtFiles</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/utfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/utfiles/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had this app for a while. In fact, this was one of the very first apps I built in Foxpro. I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted it because I wanted to get it cleaned up and add in some of the new things I&amp;rsquo;ve learned.
It&amp;rsquo;s basically a file sorting utility that takes files from a specified source directory and its subdirectories, and places them in the destination&amp;rsquo;s subdirectories based on the file&amp;rsquo;s extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GetHtml</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/gethtml/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/gethtml/</guid>
      <description>Another little program released. This program is for retrieving the HTML of a web page.
After experimenting with the West Wind Internet and Client Tools and then with my own version of a wininet.dll wrapper, I decided the easiest way was to use the WinHTTP service. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know it existed until I found it on Calvin Hsia&amp;rsquo;s Weblog.
Below is the main code of the application. Look at the links provided in the readme for more information on the oHTTP object instantiated in the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmtpTester</title>
      <link>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/smtptester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deciacco.github.io/posts/smtptester/</guid>
      <description>Ok&amp;hellip;so here it is&amp;hellip;the first of hopefully many applications you can download.
The idea to create this app came to me while I was trying to troubleshoot my uncle’s program that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t connect to his smtp server.
His application was in VB6 and he used it to send out emails from a list of addresses in an Access database. After he switched ISP&amp;rsquo;s he could no longer get it to work since the new provider required him to authenticate before being able to send mail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
